Brian, you spent a lot of time with the
media today
and my biggest takeaway is that
everything
you do here in free agency, in the
draft, and beyond is about one thing,
[music]
winning. Now, is that accurate?
>> Absolutely.
[cheering]
>> We have a very good football team and
and we are in a at a time where we think
we have a chance.
Now, one of the headlines going into the
draft, which this is all about, is that
you don't have a firstrounder, but you
do [music] have Micah Parsons, which is
one hecky consolation prize. IT IS A
MICAH BARIAN'S PROJECT.
>> But something I've read about this draft
in particular is at the top the pickings
are kind of slim, [music] but it gets
better as you go. Is this actually a
decent year not to have a first round
draft choice if such a year exists? I'll
say this from the Ted Thompson Ron Roll
score. I want as many first round picks
as we can have. But I do know no matter
where we pick, whether it's in the first
round, second round, seventh round,
there'll be a good player there that can
help the Packers. And and our job is to
make sure the next uh 60 days or so that
um that we know who those players are.
Your last comment, it's so true. Players
are where you find them. And I think
about a guy in recent times like Evan
Williams, fourth round pick, and he's a
terrific player. Players are where you
find them, aren't they?
>> Yeah, absolutely. You can look
throughout any draft, any team, and
there's players that come from all over
that can impact the team, not only in
year one, but in beyond. [cheering]
>> Middle.
>> Oh, yes.
>> In the past, you've said that the
interviews and the medicals are the most
important thing going on down here. And
when it comes to [music] those
interviews, if you are on the other side
of things, what would you give them as
the if you [music] want to nail your
interview, what are the dos and don'ts?
Cuz you've been listening to them
[music] for decades.
>> Yeah. My advice to all these guys would
be your authentic self, right? I think
that's the thing that uh you want more
than anything is to to really get to
know who they are because more than
anything, I think as a player and as a
club, you want it to be the right fit.
>> [screaming]
>> We've seen the past couple seasons how
valuable your backup [music] quarterback
can be and assuming Malik Willis is
gone. How do you look at that position
as it stands right now?
>> Yeah, if that were to happen, you know,
he'll be a tough guy to replace. [music]
Over the two years that we had him, he
was put in, you know, really tough
situations [music] and came out with
wins for us and played exceptionally
well. MALIK WELLIS DOING IT ALL.
>> I think that's very very important um to
have a guy that can go in that the team
feels confident can go [music] win a
football game and we've had that the
past two years with Malik. The
quarterback position is such an
important part of a football team. We
never stopped trying to [music] add
talent at that position.
Free agents, guys like Quay [music]
Walker, Romeo Dos, Rasheed Walker, Shawn
Ryan among others. You've got some tough
calls to make. You can't pay them all.
Where does that process lie right now?
>> At the end of the day, we're going to
try to do make the best decisions for
the Green Bay Packers. And all those
guys have done a wonderful job. Losing
any player is always a tough thing, but
that's life in the National Football
League. There's a ton of movement. And
we talk about it all the time as we
leave February meetings for the combine.
This isn't the end. This is the
beginning.